[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1.",
    "question": "I _____ a teacher.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "are", "were"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2.",
    "question": "She _____ a talented artist.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "are", "were"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3.",
    "question": "They _____ studying for the test last night.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "are", "were"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4.",
    "question": "The helping verb \"is\" should be used with singular subjects in the present time.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5.",
    "question": "She _____ finished her homework.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "has", "have"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6.",
    "question": "\"Were\" is a helping verb used in the past time (yesterday or last month).",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7.",
    "question": "The students _____ completed their assignments.",
    "options": ["is", "are", "has", "have"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8.",
    "question": "The helping verb \"am\" is used with ______.",
    "options": ["I", "You", "He", "They"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9.",
    "question": "She _____ a math test this afternoon.",
    "options": ["were", "was", "has", "none of the above"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10.",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a helping verb?",
    "options": ["Which", "Was", "Have", "Are"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q11.",
    "question": "\"Are\" is a helping verb used with plural subjects in the present time.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q12.",
    "question": "I _____ done my homework.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "has", "have"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q13.",
    "question": "The helping verb \"was\" is used to show something that happened in the past.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q14.",
    "question": "\"Have\" is a helping verb used to show the present time.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q15.",
    "question": "The kids _____ playing in the park.",
    "options": ["is", "was", "are", "has"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q16.",
    "question": "Which of the following helping verbs is used with singular subjects?",
    "options": ["Am", "Are", "Were", "None of the above"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q17.",
    "question": "They _____ visited the museum last year.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "has", "had"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q18.",
    "question": "Which of the following is a helping verb?",
    "options": ["When", "Where", "Were", "Whom"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q19.",
    "question": "The cat _____ sleeping on the couch.",
    "options": ["is", "had", "are", "were"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q20.",
    "question": "\"Are\" is a helping verb used with singular subjects.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q21.",
    "question": "The teacher _____ given the students their assignments.",
    "options": ["has", "have", "had", "none of the above"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q22.",
    "question": "The dog _____ barking all night.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "are", "was"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q23.",
    "question": "I _____ been to the park before.",
    "options": ["am", "has", "have", "had"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q24.",
    "question": "The clothes _____ washed and folded.",
    "options": ["am", "is", "has", "were"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q25.",
    "question": "The helping verb \"is\" is used with the subject to describe the past action.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": 1
  }
]
